It has begun! The Amby Challenge!
Yay!
Clap
Applause
Yes, so today's Ambey Challenge is.
Yes, sir.
Abandoned Chicken
Dumped chicken.
What do you mean by "abandoned chicken"?
Mr. Suzuki, what is "abandoned chicken"?
Abandoned chickens...
Abandoned chickens.
Abandoned! Abandoned! Abandoned!
Yes, yes, yes.
Chicken Oodai
Chicken-o'-dai.
How so?
Abandoned keeper.
What's that?
Abandoned henpeckers.
Clever girl.
Girl.
Yes.
Stage Drinks
Yes, so you all are totally different.
What is a stage drink?
It's a stage drink.
If you hear the word "stage drink" from everyone
What is it? What is it?
But it's true.
It's not just for idols.
It is indispensable for anyone who performs on stage.
When you're performing for a long time
You have to drink water, right?
Yes.
It's something you can find on the stage.
How many bottles of water do you keep on the stage for each show?
How many bottles of water did we have?
Eight bottles.
Two bottles each?
Of course we drink during the MC.
But more often than not, we drink between songs.
We often drink between songs.
So that we can drink between songs.
We put them at the top and bottom of the stage.
so that we can drink at any time.
That's right, that's right.
So everyone can have a drink at the top and the bottom.
The drinks are different, aren't they?
No, they're different.
Yes, sir.
Yuzu, by the way.
Yuzu, by the way...
For your MC position...
water only
And on the other side of the nose
This Pocari
on the other side of his nose.
Before...
I used to mix Pocari with water.
But lately...
I've been performing really hard.
When I can drink it
I don't have time to drink
I don't have time to drink at all.
I often forget to drink.
And when that happens...
Pocari is more rechargeable.
Even if I drink a little bit.
It's so rechargeable.
I think I'll stick to these two these days.
What about you, Mayuka?
Yes, I put the water at the MC position.
on the side of the MC position.
On the other side, I put Pocari water
and water on the other side.
I guess? and water on the other side.
Pocari is the best.
It's really good for your strength.
Since I drank it.
I've really become
I'm full of energy.
And the sugar, too.
I lose focus a little bit after I drink water.
Yeah, yeah.
That's when you want it.
I mix it in.
My voice trainer, Dr. Nariko, recommends it.
She recommends something like Throat Coat.
It's like a tea.
and put it in water.
and add citric acid.
I often put it in the MC position
On the other side
I put plain water on the other side.
on the other side.
That's the MC position.
Yes, because I have a lot of paper hands.
I have a lot of paper hands.
I can charge it with citric acid.
Throat.
Good for any of them in the coat.
I'll take the one like that.
I can go for paper hands, too.
Throat is a little bit unique
It has a unique taste, doesn't it?
Yeah, the first time I drank it
I really couldn't drink it.
It was too unique.
But I got used to it.
It's the most effective.
I drink a lot of this.
I drink, uh, one bottle of water.
MCH stuff?
Yeah. Depends on the day.
It's kind of random, isn't it?
It's random.
The other bottle is Pocari, Throat, water, and Citric acid, all mixed together.
All mixed?
All of it.
All of it, please.
One time. What do you want me to do? Kojima-san?
So you're just going to say "all of it"?
Is it good? I think so.
I'm not picky.
All of it, really.
That's right. I'm not picky.
Everyone says I'm picky.
Let's put it in for now.
The flowers are a little...
You know how often people say they want to put in a little bit of everything?
That's right.
Let's just put everything in for now.
I don't mind the taste of flowers.
It's delicious.
I don't know. It's so good, I want to drink it.
It's a little sweet tea.
I want to drink it because it tastes good, not because I want to drink it when my throat gets tired.
I want to drink it.
That's right.
But... I mean, this is a must for tea.
You don't often put this in.
I've seen other idols throw it away
But when I was working in Namie...
Aaryn might be the Jasmine tea type.
She's definitely the jasmine tea type.
That's why I think...
I'd like to be a backup dancer for Momokuro.
or when I was the opening act.
I'd go up on stage for rehearsals.
But when I saw Momoguro-san throw away the tea...
It's all muddy tea.
I know.
No one's drinking water.
Here it is.
Sakura Seta, the back-up dancer.
Sakura Seta was drinking Coke.
During rehearsal.
She drank a lot of Coke.
They were all drinking water or something.
I don't know about March.
I don't know about March, but he drank a Coke at rehearsal.
I don't know... they're all so stylish.
They're so cute.
They don't drink Coke sometimes.
We drink a lot.
It's actually good for our throats.
But it's more powerful... and it's my favorite bird to throw away.
We've been told for a long time that we're not allowed to drink anything but water.
That's why I'm a little jealous of all the other birdwatchers out there.
I want to do it! I have so many things I want to drink.
So today, we asked everyone to prepare the most powerful concoction they've ever made.
YEAH!
My strongest throw away chicken is Janko-no-mono, hunting water, and Manuka honey.
I can't help it, it's my mom's special drink! It's already honey, but I don't know why she's doing it...
I found this on sns from a guy who does voicemail.
She found this on sns and bought it for me!
And then...
Just try it.
My mom does it all the time. I don't do it anymore.
Now, here's a special guest, Moe Suzuki, your mom.
She's not here.
We'll have to call her and ask.
She said it's all here.
I can do it.
You should really put all of this in there.
You know what, Mom?
Hello?
Mai mai!
Hello, Maima.
Hello.
I'm working on a recipe for the discarded chickens at the Amechare,
Moka told me that she always brings the honey that her mom makes from the discarded chickens,
Today, you put it in a cup again, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Moka, I wanted to ask you if it's okay to put all the honey in this cup, and how much of the mixture is good.
What?
Mixing.
Maybe, uh, let's see.
I usually put 2, 2, 3 spoons in a 500 ml container.
Well, that's pretty neat, isn't it?
You did it right.
I said it's absolutely proper, like you said before.
Did you do it right?
Properly.
Generally, yes.
Okay, um, half a bottle of Aquarius tequina and a glass of water.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
No, thank you very much.
Cute.
I definitely don't want anyone to see this.
Just a word.
A word?
To the viewers.
Thank you for always enjoying Amechale!
Yes!
So this is how you always do it.
Okay, bye-bye.
That was so nice of you.
I'm really sorry, I can't do anything.
It's like a reflection of something.
It's always like this. There was something you couldn't do.
Mom, I was thinking. I didn't know. I thought it was just fine.
Did it always taste the same? It was the same, that's for sure.
I'll see what I can do. Is this the same one, because it's not 500 ml. It's not 500 ml.
I drink something like this all the time.
Nice. Looks good.
I wonder if you can make it for me when I have a singing job or something.
Ta-da! It's ready!
Just by the looks of it. It always looked like this.
Now let's drink!
Bon appétit!
It's a little thin, but it tastes the same as usual.
It's true that I didn't put any kokari in it.
I should have added a little more honey.
Next is miso!
Let's see...
A little more...
If it tastes like this...
Is it too weak?
It's good with honey.
Oh, really?
It's good.
I've heard it's good for the Palace, so I take it to ease my mind.
Maybe next time you'll do that too.
Oh, I'll try that one more time.
Mana touched it a little bit, so...
Hana said she wanted to drink, and then she said, "Pico pico.
I want Hana to make that one now, too.
I found something.
How long was that?
I'll be back with, uh, Fairytale!
I'll catch you.
It's no good.
It doesn't work.